Guide to the Ronald Shiffman collection on the Pratt Center for Community Development 2013.023
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 3: Community Development
  - Sub-series 3.2: Specific Programs
    - South Asian Americans Chhaya Community Development Center, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - St. Nicholas Neighborhood Preservation Corporation, 1984-1993 (Box 53, Folder 10-11)
    - Strategy for a Coordinated Social and Physical Renewal Program: Bedford-Stuyvesant, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Streetwatch, New Cities Community Development Corporation, undated (Box 143, Item 403)
    - Stuyvesant Heights, A Good Neighborhood in Need of Help, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - The Bedford-Stuyvesant Community Rehabilitation Planning Program, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Thomas, Franklin, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - University Year for Action, 1974-1981 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Urban Homesteading Assistance Board (UHAB), 1976-1992 (Box 54, Folder 1-5)
    - Urban Homesteading Assistance Board (UHAB) Tax Shelters, Undated (Box 53, Folder 16-17)
  - Sub-series 3.3: History Projects
    - A Practical Man, 1995 (Box 142, Item 467)
      VHS. Runtime: 0:46:14
    - A Profile of New York City, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Audiophile -- Nancy Community Development Corporations, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Community Improvements, 1966-1998 (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration, circa 1990 (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - Brochures Sent to Funders, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 17)
    - Building Hope Andrea Research, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 36)
    - Building Hope Contact Sheet, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 19)
    - Building Hope Contact Sheet -- Requests to be Answered, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 20)
    - Building Hope Correspondences, 1993-1994 (Box 112, Folder 21)
    - Building Hope Draft Outreach Plan, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 22)
    - Building Hope Ford Foundation Agreement, 1993 (Box 112, Folder 23)
    - Building Hope Mailing Materials -- National Community Development Network, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 24)
    - Building Hope Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 25)
    - Building Hope National Network Mailing Lists, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 26)
    - Building Hope New York Metro Area PR, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 27)
    - Building Hope Oral History Project CDCs Interviewed Address List, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 28)
    - Building Hope Oral History Project Outline for Profiles, 1990-1995 (Box 112, Folder 29)
    - Building Hope Order Form, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 30)
    - Building Hope Orders, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 32)
    - Building Hope Orders Cover Letter, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 31)
    - Building Hope Photo Permission Letter, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 33)
    - Building Hope Posters, 1995 (Box 112, Folder 34)
    - Building Hope Profile Memo, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 35)
    - Building Hope Releases, Cue Sheets, and Copyright Research, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 18)
    - Building Hope Resumes, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 37)
    - Building Hope Stock Footage, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 38)
    - Building Hope Summaries and Treatments, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 39)
    - Building Hope Sunday Notes, Undated (Box 112, Folder 40)
    - Building Hope Titles, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 41)
    - Building Hope: Community Development in America, 1968-1997 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Building Hope: Community Development in America, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - CDC Oral History -- Building Hope, 1983-1989 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - CDC Oral History -- Building Hope, 1983-1989 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - CDC Oral History Documentary Asian Americans for Equality Doris Koo, 1991 (Box 112, Folder 41)
    - CDC Oral History Documentary Chicanos Por La Causa Joe Eddie Lopez, 1991 (Box 112, Folder 42)
    - CDC Oral History Documentary Chicanos Por La Causa Pete Garcia, 1991 (Box 112, Folder 43)
    - CDC Oral History Documentary Chicanos Por La Causa Ronnie Lopez, 1991 (Box 112, Folder 44)
    - CDC Oral History Documentary Chicanos Por La Causa Tommy Espinoza, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - CDC Oral History Documentary Drew Economic Development Corporation Brenda Shockley, 1990 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - CDC Oral History Documentary Drew Economic Development Corporation Carla Dartis, 1990 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - CDC Oral History Documentary Missippi Action for Community Education Larry Farmer, 1990 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - CDC Oral History Documentary Missippi Action for Community Education Unita Blackwell, 1990 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - CDC Oral History Documentary Preproduction, 1992 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - CDC Oral History Transcript -- David Lizarraga, 1990 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - CDC Oral History Transcript -- Dowdy, 1990 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - CDC Oral History Transcripts -- Mexican American Unity Council Juan Patlan, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - CDC Oral History Transcripts -- Mexican American Unity Council Royce Mahula, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - CDC Oral History Transcripts -- South East Alabama Self-Help Association John Brown, 1990 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - CDC Oral History Transcripts -- South East Development Incorporated Betty Hyatt, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - CDC Oral History Transcripts -- South East Development Incorporated Roberth Gilloth, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - CDC Oral History Transcripts -- Southern Cooperative Development Fund A.J. McKnight, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - CDC Oral History Transcripts -- Southern Cooperative Development Fund Marvin Beaulieu, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - CDC Oral History Transcripts -- Spanish Speaking Unity Council Arabella Martinez, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - CDC Oral History Transcripts -- Spanish Speaking Unity Council Henry Mestre, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - CDC Oral History Transcripts -- Spanish Speaking Unity Council Herman Gallegos, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - CDC Oral History Transcripts -- The Advisory Committee of Liberty City Youth Otis Pitts, Jr., 1991 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - CDC Oral History Transcripts -- The East Los Angeles Community Union Esteban Torres, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - CDC Oral History Transcripts -- The Woodlawn Organization Arthur Brazier, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - CDC Oral History Transcripts -- The Woodlawn Organization Lauren Allen, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - CDC Oral History Transcripts -- The Woodlawn Organization Leon Finney, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - CDC Oral History Transcripts -- United Durham Incorporated Nathan Taylor Garrett, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - CDC Oral History Transcripts -- United Durham Incorporated Richmond Edward Stewart, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - CDC Oral History Transcripts -- Watts Labor Community Action Committee Ted Watkins, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - CDC Oral History Transcripts -- Zion Investment Association Sullivan, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Community Development Corporation Oral History Project, 1990-1994 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Community Development Corporation Oral History Project and Profiles, 1972-1997 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Community Development Corporation Profile Introductory Brochure, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Community Development Corporation Profiles Final Drafts Send to Organizations, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Community Development Corporation Profiles Outreach, 1995-1996 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - Discussion by Advisory Board Members, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Evolution of Community Controlled Housing Development Ron 11-1985 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Ford Foundation Oral History and Community Development, 1987-1988 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Ford Foundation Oral History Project 2nd Grant Request, 1989-1994 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Ford Foundation Oral History Project Final Reports on Grant Number 2, 1992-1995 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Ford Foundation Oral History Project Progess Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Ford Foundation Oral History Project Proposal, 1888 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Hatch Article in the Scope of Social Architecture, Undated (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Interview with Ron Shiffman Transcript, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Mexican American Community Council Drafts, 1995 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Profile Information Community Development Corporations, 1990-1995 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Oral History Admin, 1996-1997 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Oral History and Community Development Corporations, 1987-1994 (Box 115, Folder 9-10)
    - Oral History Project A Practical Man Brochure, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Outreach and Education Handouts, 1995-1996 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - PICCED Anniversary Conference, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - PICCED History, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - PICCED History -- Ron's Appointment to City Planning Commission 1991, 1992-1998 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - PICCED Timeline, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Pratt Center Administrative Materials, 1984-1991 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Pratt Center Files -- Legal and Financial Issues, 1991-1993 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Pratt Center Institute for Community and Environment Development Highlights 1996-97, 1996-1997 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Pratt Institute Real Movies, Inc. -- A Practical Man, 1995 (Box 143, Item 387)
    - Preservation Pub Interview Ron Shiffman, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Printed Drafts of Community Development Corporation Profiles for Limited Distribution, 1990-1995 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Rebuilding the South Bronx: The Story of Southeast Bronx Community Organization, undated (Box 142, Item 410)
      VHS color. Runtime: 0:14:00
    - Request for PBS's America's War on Poverty, 1995 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Resource Center Technology, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Restoration Tour -- Watkins Interview PICCED, undated (Box 140, Item 326)
      Hi8 Cassette. Runtime: 2:00:00
    - Southern Development Corporation, 1994 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Strategic Planning Process, 1987-1992 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Unedited Interview For the Voice of America, undated (Box 138, Item 476)
    - Various Ron Shiffman Statements, 1967-1995 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Various Ron Shiffman Statements, 1989-2015 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Sub-series 3.4: Building Hope Audio-Visual Recordings
    - The Advisory Committee of Liberty City Youth Economic Development Corporation, undated (Box 125, Item 124)
    - The Advisory Committee of Liberty City Youth Economic Development Corporation, undated (Box 125, Item 126)
    - The Advisory Committee of Liberty City Youth Economic Development Corporation, undated (Box 122, Item 114)
    - The Advisory Committee of Liberty City Youth Economic Development Corporation, Belafonte, Crime Prevention Workshop and Miscellaneous Visuals -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 124, Item 108)
      Betacam SP NTSC Mono. Runtime: 1:00:00
    - The Advisory Committee of Liberty City Youth Economic Development Corporation, Otis Pitts Jr #! -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 126, Item 141)
      Betacam SP NTSC Stereo. Runtime: 1:00:00
    - The Advisory Committee of Liberty City Youth Economic Development Corporation, Otis Pitts Jr #2 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 124, Item 107)
    - The Advisory Committee of Liberty City Youth Economic Development Corporation, Pitts, undated (Box 125, Item 125)
    - The Advisory Committee of Liberty City Youth Economic Development Corporation, Pitts, undated (Box 122, Item 115)
    - The Advisory Committee of Liberty City Youth Economic Development Corporation, Pitts, undated (Box 122, Item 116)
    - Anna Faith Jones #1 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 139, Item 320)
    - Anna Faith Jones #2 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 139, Item 321)
    - Asian Americans for Equality, undated (Box 120, Item 052)
    - Asian Americans for Equality, Koo #1-3, undated (Box 119, Item 041)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation -- Elsie Richardson #3 and Ron Shiffman #1, undated (Box 139, Item 324)
      Betacam.
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation -- Rich Photos, undated (Box 135, Item 269)
      U-matic S. Runtime: 0:20:00
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation Tour -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, 1996 (Box 117, Item 040)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation Tour #2 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 136, Item 465)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Ben Glascoe, part 2; Judge Thomas Jones, part 1, undated (Box 139, Item 454)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Bernard McDonald #2 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 139, Item 458)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Bernard McDonald #3 and Elsie Richardson #1 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 139, Item 459)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, DOAR #1-2, undated (Box 134, Item 244)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, DOAR #3-4, undated (Box 133, Item 231)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Elsie Richardson #2 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 136, Item 460)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Franklin Thomas #2 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 136, Item 463)
      Betacam SP. Runtime: 0:39:00
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Franklin Thomas #3 and Cutaways -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 136, Item 464)
      Betacam SP. Runtime: 1:00:00
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Glascoe #1-3, undated (Box 120, Item 046)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Glascoe #4-5, undated (Box 120, Item 047)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, John Doar #1, undated (Box 139, Item 452)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, John Doar #1, undated (Box 140, Item 473)
      VHS SP. Runtime: 1:00:00
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, John Doar #1, undated (Box 140, Item 474)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, John Doar #2 and Ben Glascoe #1, undated (Box 139, Item 453)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Jones #1-2, undated (Box 133, Item 232)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Jones #3-4, undated (Box 133, Item 233)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Jones #5-6, undated (Box 133, Item 234)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Jones #7-8, undated (Box 119, Item 043)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Jones #9, undated (Box 134, Item 252)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Judge Thomas Jones, part 2, undated (Box 139, Item 455)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Judge Thomas Jones, part 3, undated (Box 139, Item 456)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Rich. #1-2, undated (Box 133, Item 230)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Rich. #3-4, undated (Box 134, Item 245)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Rich. #5-6, undated (Box 119, Item 044)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Ron Shiffman #2 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 136, Item 461)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Ron Shiffman #3 and Franklin Thomas #1 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 136, Item 462)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Shiffman #1-2, undated (Box 120, Item 045)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Shiffman #5-6, undated (Box 133, Item 236)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Shiffman Interview #3-4, undated (Box 120, Item 053)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Street Life, undated (Box 133, Item 235)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Street Life, undated (Box 134, Item 246)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Street Life, undated (Box 134, Item 247)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Street Shots, undated (Box 134, Item 243)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Thomas #1-2, undated (Box 133, Item 237)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Thomas #3-4, undated (Box 133, Item 238)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, Thomas #5-6, undated (Box 120, Item 054)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation: Judge Thomas Jones, part 4; Bernard McDonald, part 1, undated (Box 139, Item 457)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Tour #3, undated (Box 136, Item 466)
    - Building Hope, December 21, 1992 (Box 131, Item 210)
      U-matic. Runtime: 0:56:40
    - Building Hope, June 10, 1993 (Box 131, Item 211)
    - Building Hope, 1994 (Box 142, Item 436)
      VHS. Runtime: 0:56:40
    - Building Hope, 1995 (Box 140, Item 472)
      VHS SECAM 625/50. Runtime: 0:56:40
    - Building Hope, 2002 (Box 138, Item 359)
      VHS. Runtime: 0:56:51
    - Building Hope -- Revised Narration Script Enclosed, June 23, 1993 (Box 131, Item 212)
      U-matic. Runtime: 0:10:00
    - Building Hope Vanguard Films, 1993 (Box 131, Item 213)
    - Building Hope, Community Development in America, 1994 (Box 142, Item 468)
      VHS. Runtime: 0:56:46
    - Building Hope: Community Development Corporations -- September 17 1993 Cut, June 17, 1993 (Box 130, Item 192)
      U-matic. Runtime: 0:18:00
    - C. Hobson Community Development Corporations Documentary WRS Animation B-Roll, 1992 (Box 137, Item 318)
    - Center for Community Change: Garland Yates, part 1; Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 139, Item 322)
    - Center for Community Change: Garland Yates, part 2; Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 139, Item 323)
    - Charles Hobson, Community Development Corporations Documentary WRS Animation Photos 2, 1992 (Box 132, Item 200)
      Betacam Small. Runtime: 0:20:00
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, undated (Box 135, Item 264)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, undated (Box 119, Item 042)
      U-matic.
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, undated (Box 120, Item 048)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, undated (Box 120, Item 050)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, undated (Box 120, Item 051)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, undated (Box 134, Item 240)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, undated (Box 134, Item 241)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, undated (Box 134, Item 249)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, undated (Box 134, Item 251)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Espinoza, undated (Box 134, Item 262)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Espinoza, undated (Box 134, Item 242)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Espinoza, undated (Box 134, Item 248)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Espinoza #1-3, undated (Box 135, Item 288)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Espinoza #4-6, undated (Box 135, Item 289)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Espinoza #7-8, undated (Box 135, Item 290)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Garcia, undated (Box 134, Item 250)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Garcia #1-2, undated (Box 120, Item 049)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Jackie Castro, Patti Garcia, Maria Salas -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 132, Item 255)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Joe Eddie Lopez -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 137, Item 281)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Lopez, undated (Box 134, Item 261)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Lopez, undated (Box 135, Item 263)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Lopez, undated (Box 135, Item 291)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Pete Garcia #1 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, 1996 (Box 137, Item 280)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Pete Garcia #1 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 137, Item 282)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Pete Garcia #2 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, 1996 (Box 137, Item 279)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Pete Garcia #2 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 137, Item 283)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Ronnie Lopez #1 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 137, Item 284)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Thomas Espinoza -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 132, Item 253)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Thomas Espinoza #1 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, 1991 (Box 137, Item 276)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Thomas Espinoza #1 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, 1991 (Box 137, Item 278)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Thomas Espinoza #2 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, 1991 (Box 137, Item 277)
    - Chicanos Por La Causa, Thomas Espinoza, Joe Eddie Lopez, undated (Box 132, Item 254)
    - Community Development Corporation - Building Hope Revised, 1993 (Box 143, Item 381)
      VHS. Runtime: 0:18:00
    - Community Development Corporation Project Rough Cut, undated (Box 143, Item 382)
    - Community Development Corporations -- McDonald, undated (Box 138, Item 358)
    - Delaware Valley Community Reinvestment Fund, Jeremy Nowak, undated (Box 132, Item 260)
    - Delaware Valley Community Reinvestment Fund, Jeremy Nowak #1 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 132, Item 272)
    - Delaware Valley Community Reinvestment Fund, Jeremy Nowak #2 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 137, Item 273)
    - Dineh Cooperatives Incorporated, undated (Box 135, Item 287)
    - Dineh Cooperatives Incorporated -- Scenery Shot, Wideshot of Arizona, undated (Box 135, Item 265)
    - Dineh Cooperatives Incorporated, Begay, undated (Box 135, Item 285)
    - Dineh Cooperatives Incorporated, Colvin, undated (Box 135, Item 286)
    - Dineh Cooperatives Incorporated, Filene Begay -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 132, Item 256)
    - Dineh Cooperatives Incorporated, Jon Calvin, undated (Box 132, Item 258)
    - Dineh Cooperatives Incorporated, Tooh Dineh Industries, TSeyi Shoppuing Center, Chinle Health Center, Window Rock Civic Center Powwow, undated (Box 132, Item 257)
    - Doris Koo -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 137, Item 319)
    - Drew Economic Development Corporation, undated (Box 135, Item 266)
    - Drew Economic Development Corporation, undated (Box 135, Item 274)
    - Drew Economic Development Corporation #1-3, undated (Box 133, Item 227)
    - Drew Economic Development Corporation Shockley Interview, undated (Box 136, Item 293)
    - Drew Economic Development Corporation, Brenda Shockley #1 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 132, Item 270)
    - Drew Economic Development Corporation, Brenda Shockley #2 -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 132, Item 271)
    - Drew Economic Development Corporation, Carla Dartis, Willowbrook Green Housing Development, Ujima Village Housing Development, Tillmon Child Care, undated (Box 132, Item 259)
    - Drew Economic Development Corporation, Shockley #1-2, undated (Box 135, Item 275)
    - Drew Economic Development Corporation, Sholkley #3-4, undated (Box 133, Item 228)
    - The East Los Angeles Community Union, undated (Box 125, Item 130)
    - The East Los Angeles Community Union, undated (Box 125, Item 121)
    - The East Los Angeles Community Union, undated (Box 125, Item 122)
    - The East Los Angeles Community Union, Baldwin Park Groundbreaking -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 123, Item 089)
    - The East Los Angeles Community Union, David Lizarraga -- Community Development Corporations Oral History Project, undated (Box 123, Item 087)